you stop?
I don't know?
Shut it up
Woah—oh—oh—ohhh.
I had hoped to avoid a battle like this.
Why were they so thoroughly prepared?
How did they know we were coming?
Perhaps I have a spy
within your castle walls.
Since I've just had my mansion built,
I'd rather not have it
turned into a battleground.
So I came all the way out
here to meet you instead.
Were you just telling me
a lie to keep me pacified?
Answer me, how clever!
A little late though, back then we
sensed we were at a major disadvantage;
you had just come back home.
And we feared if you joined
forces with the yoguro,
we'd have to deal with the
samurai and yakuza together.
Considering we had fewer
numbers at that time,
it would have been an
uphill battle for our side,
especially if you lived
up to your fearsome
reputation as a madman who doesn't blink.
Sacrifice only a fool would
rush into those circumstances;
luckily for us,
we took Orochi's words
at face value and chose
the path where you thought
no one would get hurt.
Newgate and Roger were cut from
the same pathetic cloth as you.
Mighty pirates but softness is a
weakness—look what you've become:
a fool who chose to dance stripped
to your loincloth and mocked by
all you've whittled away what little
dignity the kozuki clan had left. I
still
stand
by my decision
that I made that day;
we're here to.
to I speak of the future, though!
I never realized how
tough someone I could be.
Don't watch out!
We have the advantage with our numbers!
Follow me! Onward!
Hurry!
Follow Lord Odin!
I gotcha now!
What was that?
Who's there?
I hope you don't mind me
stepping in to help a bit.
It is sudden, and you
probably don't remember me.
I served Lord Tsukiyaki when he was alive.
You're Shinobu from the Ninja Legion?
Yes!
That would be me!
What happened to the others?
Why are you here alone?
It's only me, unfortunately.
Fukurokuju chose to ally
himself with Orochi.
I cannot fault him for losing faith
in a foolish lord such as myself.
Long have I dreamed of the day that
you take over as Shogun, my lord.
I am loyal to the Kozakis.
Know we walk the path of thorns, Shura.
I'm well aware of that.
I devote myself entirely.
Let's press onward!
A messenger delivered an unsettling
letter from your husband.
It read, My wife and
children are in danger.
Please save them.
How dare you!
Momono, or rather Lord
Momonosuke, is already eight.
My lady, we should prepare for the work.
Odin's defeat would be
more than a simple setback.
It would be the end of our country.
First unit here, they
were too much for us.
Sorry sir, we never imagined
Kozuki Odin would be this strong.
What a bunch of weaklings.
Thousands of troops versus 11
samurai, and they still can't cut it.
How are they giving
them this much trouble?
It's too pathetic to watch.
Let me handle it.
Last breath.
Kozuki Oden.
I've been waiting to
meet someone like you.
I'm here to kill you!
Your reign over the land
of water will end today!
Hold in two-sword style!
Paradise Polska!
That bastard actually landed
a hit on Commander Kaido!
Time to finish you all!
Karoo!!
Kaido!!
Never come back to Waro!!
Father!!
Help me!
Turn around!
He's hurting me!
Warmo!!
Washington.
It's me.
Lord Odin.
My lord, I failed him.
And thus ends the final
battle of Kozuki Oden,
who collapsed in defeat
beside his loyal retainers.
the battle between the
beast pirates and samurai
was so intense that it
set the forest of udon
ablaze in fact the inferno
did not die down until
rain fell upon the land
a full five days later
mother
do you think father will
be home soon i made a
toy for him did you see
my would you look at that
i bet you miss your father
The daimyo of Kuri,
Kozuki Oden, and his nine followers
were imprisoned in the flower capital.
Now labeled criminals,
they were to await their death sentence
for rebelling against the shogun.
Unaware of the reason for their
arrest, the population reacted coldly.
Odin was a disappointment.
It's too little too late.
So we don't even get to
see his asinine dance
anymore But that was the
only thing he was good for.
Don't mock the simple-minded
Sorry, sorry.
I've never seen this woman.
How can someone I've
never met be my retainer?
Are you making an attempt
on my life as well?
Lord Oden...
I don't know what your
plan is, but drop the act!
Be gone from my sight, Kunoichi!
Attention everyone!
The sentences have been
decided for the Samurai!
The ten immoral insurgents who dared
to rise against the Shogun Orochi
shall receive swift and just punishment
for their wicked transgressions.
In 72 hours, the offenders shall face
execution by being boiled to death!
three days later this
isn't something you get
to see often since
they're using hot oil it
won't take long then we better hurry no it
has yet to be tasted for
poison please allow me
excuse me mother i don't understand why
somebody would be after her family's lives
Your father's a great man.
Momonosuke, one day you
will rule this land.
Then you'll understand.
Here you go.
It's safe for consumption.
Thank you so much for the food.
Are you okay?
Mother!
Be honest!
Please, come home.
The public execution of
the rebellious Kozuki Odin
and his nine retainers
shall begin momentarily.
Despite his best efforts,
he couldn't take down Kaido.
He might have been a fool, but he was
pretty tough when it came down to it.
I don't know, but look where
his strength landed him!
Give me a chance to live.
I must.
I must live!
How dare you!
I make the calls around here!
It's too late to start
begging for your life.
Now get in the pot!
Help me!
All ten of us will enter the pot together.
I'll attempt to withstand
it for an agreed time.
Whoever survives may go.
Do we have a deal?
Are you stupid?
The oil's going to kill you instantly!
You think you've got a chance?
You're crazy!
This is too pathetic to watch.
Seems Odin has stooped
to a new low. All right.
Someone fetch me a timer. Yes, sir!
Kaido, are you sure?
Just trust me.
Looks like this is your
chance to make history.
Let's see how long you last.
I'll give you one hour.
You think you can hold out?
That's too long even for a normal bath.
A fool to the end, I see.
Do I have your word?
Of course you do.
Please, talk to us first!
Come back!
Please, we beg you!
He survived!
Do not let him suffer on his own!
We must follow our Lord.
We shall meet again in the
next world. Farewell! Great!
Stay back!
Balance yourselves on this plank!
All of you!
Lord!
What are you doing, my lord? Stop!
We're ready to die!
Please, my lord!
This is cruel!
It's a disgrace to live on without you!
My lord, we should be holding you, Garam!
Please, switch with me!
You should allow me to go in your stead!
Please, Lord Odin!
Shut up and stay pot!
That's an order!
But our duty as our retainers
should be to protect you!
Do not start questioning me! Please!
Oh, that filthy cheater!
These damn retainers aren't
even touching the oil!
Well, I have to hand it to him.
All ten are in the pot.
Clever, Odin.
Fair enough.
All right, let's start the clock.
This isn't fair.
Please, my lord, let us down!
Think you'll last.
It has been a bit of a minute yet.
He's still standing.
His skin is tough.
I fear I may faint from this heat alone.
I can't take it.
You gotta have no right to
complain, so suck it up, Race.
Sit still.
You gotta have it easy.
Stop your wiggling, cat.
We have to stay balanced up here.
Lord Odin.
Man, I thought they were
supposed to burn up instantly.
This is taking too long.
Shouldn't there be more
pain and suffering?
How's this supposed to be entertaining?
Would you hurry up already, you damn fool?
We're sick of you! Just end it!
How dare you!
Are you calling Odin a fool?
If you do that again, I'll end you!
I'm sorry.
What is she gonna do? No!
She's seriously gonna cut that guy!
Is she a Kunoichi?
Do you see? Shinobu.
What is this about?
Why has she revealed herself?
I should cut that tongue out of your head!
You don't know the truth!
The only fool here is you!
You live in peace and
none of you know why!
Who the hell do you think ensured that?
Pray that we don't lose Lord Odin today!
You don't know the burden he carries!
You'll soon understand how much
suffering he's kept at bay!
Listen to me, Orochi
never wanted to be Shogun.
It's hard to believe, but he
had no intention of ruling Wano.
Every last person in this damn
country mistreated the Kurozumi clan.
They're all guilty of persecution.
They are all scum.
I couldn't care less if
every last one of them dies.
Would you like to know
why I became the Shogun?
Surprise, surprise!
To get my revenge!
I'll send this country straight to hell!
My grandfather had a dream!
He wanted to become Shogun, you know!
That was long before you were born!
He poisoned every daimyo one
by one before he was caught.
Then the damned shogun
forced him to commit seppuku.
Our clan lost its status.
That's fair enough.
But what happened next was
a living nightmare for us.
It was senseless cruelty.
The members of our clan were chased
down and terrorized by complete
strangers who claimed they were
taking the law into their own hands.
They beat us, threw us in
the river, struck us dead.
I was so terrified of this vigilante
mob that I couldn't sleep at night.
But my grandfather's
crime had been paid for.
He was long dead.
You'll pay to Rosamy.
We'll kill you all.
Aaaaaaahhh!
Your bloodline is evil!
You're a Daimyo killer!
It's not my fault!
Doesn't matter if you're a child!
You're a criminal if you're a Kurozumi!
You see why I seek revenge now, do you?
Every less person in
Wano will feel my fury!
What is this?
You're a madman.
I am bringing them the
punishment they deserve!
Orochi, what are you
planning to do with them?
In another room, Orochi
was stockpiling weapons,
along with hundreds of people
who had been kidnapped.
Once handed over, their fate was sealed.
Their very humanity was taken from them.
They became tributes.
All given away to Kaido.
Oh, those people?
They'll be sold and tortured.
Some killed, perhaps.
Lord Odin was furious.
But Orochi has stopped the
conflict by making a proposal.
Do you want Bono to go to war?
Think, Odin.
Or would you like the kidnappings to stop?
I'd choose wisely if I were you.
There's a lot on the line here.
He was driven by hate.
A cruel act of vengeance.
By our pain.
Win or lose.
Orochi would cause unspeakable
suffering to this country.
Lord Odin's hand was forced.
He had no other choice.
He danced like a fool every week
as an apology to the Kurozumi clan.
He knew by doing so he
would lose his standing.
But that didn't matter.
He could save 100 lives with each dance.
He trusted Orochi's promise that five years
later, when their ships were finished,
they would leave Wano and never return.
But he put too much faith in them.
He traveled region to region every week,
ensuring that everything was in order.
The entire time, Lord Odin
has been protecting Wano.
So why don't you tell me again?
Who are you calling a fool?
Let's go.
Lord Odin protected us, but
what are we supposed to do?
Why would you tell us this now?
All this is way too hard to swallow.
Let me go!
The truth will only create
strife for this country.
Go to hell!
A foolish lord rebelled against
the Shogun and was punished.
That's what people will say.
We'll be dead in moments,
and all will be settled.
Surely you knew you
would face consequences.
You think I'm afraid?
I'm one of Lord Odin's retainers!
I share my fate with them!
Why would I listen to the
barking of Orochi's dogs?
I am prepared to die beside my lord,
but that doesn't mean I'm giving up!
You watch.
All of us will survive, and then
we'll bring an end to your treachery!
Hmm, what a joke.
Shogun, please!
Stop the execution!
This isn't right!
I beg of you, my lord!
Please, my lord!
Someone call a doctor!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Orochi!
They were nothing but scum.
It was not only the Shogun's family
who persecuted the Kurozumi clan,
but the common people as well.
So when Orochi turned his ire upon them,
they immediately realized what kind of
suffering his vengeance
might bring to the land.
Meanwhile, thanks to
Shinobu's passionate words,
the truth behind Odin's naked
dancing spread quickly throughout
the city and the hearts of
the people began to change.
What then?
He was the one who saved us that day.
We mocked him for all those
years and he never said a word.
He was suffering more than anyone
and he carried that all on his own.
We're fools.
What have we done?
From all directions, the
citizens rushed to Odin,
knowing now that the daimyo of Conney
is not the fool they thought he was.
They were filled with regret, and as this
brave samurai stood before their eyes,
facing death, they realized that he was the
only hope left for the future of Warner.
Lord Odin, you can't leave us!
I'm sorry for every wrong
thing I said about you.
Thank you for keeping
everyone safe all these years.
It's far too late now.
You bunch of brown nosers!
Ignore them and just...
Thank you everyone.
I shall give him my best.
He's so honorable.
Far from being moved by their pleas,
Orochi could not let the people's
sudden support of Oden go unpunished.
Before they knew it, they were surrounded
by Kaido and Orochi subordinates.
Swords at their back.
They could only stare upon
the cruel execution in terror.
The temperature of the oil rose above a
thousand degrees and continued to climb.
Swift Arrows carried news of the
events to the leaders of each region.
The Letter Arrows Wano fly great
distances with extreme accuracy.
Listen, well, if I survive
this execution by some means,
I will change this country.
I will open up the land
of Wano to the world.
What are those idiots
battling about over there?
You have said before that the borders
of this land should be opened again.
And yet, you also said that our policy
of isolation is tied to the Kozuki clan.
When you traveled the seas
with Whitebeard and Roger,
what secrets of the world did you uncover?
Many years ago,
the ones who decided
that this country should
close its borders were
indeed the Kozuki clan.
They sought to protect the land of Wano
from an outside force of overwhelming might.
But now this country, or rather the world,
awaits the arrival of a
figure of great importance.
Once the promised 800 years
have passed, they will appear.
And when they do,
this country must be welcoming to
them and ready to work by their side.
I will be clear with you.
Today will not be a victory,
for I am certain that
they are going to kill me.
Hey, Lord!
Stop it!
You have the strength to survive this!
A third of the time has already passed!
Take up the cause in my stead.
You must open the land of Wano.
We'll do it, but we'll do it by your side.
We have heard your dream.
And it shall be our dream as well.
Well spoken, my friend.
All right.
Thirty minutes to go.
The boiling oil that cooked Odin's
flesh created a living hell,
not only for him, but his retainers.
This is absurd!
Hurry!
Raise the temperature, you dolds!
Only ten minutes left!
Why in the hell are you so tough?
Burn already!
Just five minutes.
One minute left!
Ten seconds!
Three seconds.
Come on.
One second!
It's a miracle!
He survived the execution!
Come on, please!
Lord Odin is too tough to boil!
He did it.
Lord Odin wins the name!
And his name has been cleared as well!
The citizens will surely take his
side now that they know the truth
Ready for a fight, eh, Kaido?
Don't taunt him, stupid cat! Why not?
We won, didn't we?
I changed my mind a minute
ago and decided to go
with Death by Firing Squad
instead of the other deer
And Odin's not the only
one we're executing!
His entire family will be killed as well!
A child is excused from a coward!
That's not what you promised!
Lord Odin bought his car!
If you've got a problem, then step up!
We've got plenty of bullets to go around!
I'm counting on you.
Make me proud!
You must open up the land of water!
Odward!
Takuri!
Jinbe!
Do not look back!
Kozuki Oden!
Pardon me, I couldn't help but
overhear what you just said.
Kill them!
Kill them all!
After them!
Kill every last member of the Kozuki clan!
No matter what happens next, your
body's already damaged beyond repair.
I'll give you a parting gift,
a nice bullet to the head.
It seems the era of
Kozuki is over for good.
All of you are dead.
You have underestimated my samurai, Kaido.
What a lord, I would hate you.
That food isn't yours.
Are you listening?
Put that back.
Whoa! I give up! I give up!
I thought you were dead!
Why must I end this way?
This hellhole is the only
home that I will ever know!
A pampered bastard like you
could never understand my life!
You're telling me this is
the life that you want!
Such cruelty!
Shame on you!
Those are children you bastards
trying to burn at the stake!
Why am I so hungry?
Because you lent all our
money and now we can't eat!
I've got it!
Steal some food and bring it back here!
A dino shouldn't say that!
Though I'm sure this is
not the end you envisioned,
people will speak of your heroic
death for generations to come.
They can call me a hero or a fool.
They can even forget me if they so please!
But...
No matter what, my spirit will live on!
I'm not proud of what
happened with that old hag.
Rest assured, she's dead.
Killed her, did you?
Well, aren't you noble?
Build your strength while you can.
I will be happy if people
tell my story over a drink.
My loyal samurai, Toki,
Momonosuke, Hiyori.
I go forth.
Alden wouldn't be Alden!
Would it be Elrond if
it wasn't for at all?
Once one legend comes to an
end, yet the story continues,
carried on by new players on a new stage.